[{"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "net.", "authority": ["k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "net.", "authority": ["k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "net.", "authority": ["g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "net.", "authority": ["d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "net.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "net.", "authority": ["g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "net.", "authority": ["h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "net.", "authority": ["j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "net.", "authority": ["k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "net.", "authority": ["b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": ["b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": "net.", "authority": []}, {"answer": ["j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": "net.", "authority": []}, {"answer": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": "net.", "authority": []}, {"answer": ["m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": "net.", "authority": []}, {"answer": ["i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": "net.", "authority": []}, {"answer": ["i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": "net.", "authority": []}, {"answer": ["c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": "net.", "authority": []}, {"answer": ["g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": "net.", "authority": []}, {"answer": ["h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": "net.", "authority": []}, {"answer": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": "net.", "authority": []}, {"answer": ["m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": "net.", "authority": []}, {"answer": ["f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": "net.", "authority": []}, {"answer": ["i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."], "flags": 33792, "question": "net.", "authority": []}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "k.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "h.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "m.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "g.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "a.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "j.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "l.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "e.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "d.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "i.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "c.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "b.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "f.gtld-servers.net.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["g.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["l.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av1.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["h.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["m.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av2.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["d.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["m.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["j.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["l.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av3.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["d.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["i.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["a.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["f.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["j.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["f.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["l.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "e.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["e.gtld-servers.net.", "c.gtld-servers.net.", "m.gtld-servers.net.", "a.gtld-servers.net.", "j.gtld-servers.net.", "l.gtld-servers.net.", "k.gtld-servers.net.", "d.gtld-servers.net.", "f.gtld-servers.net.", "h.gtld-servers.net.", "b.gtld-servers.net.", "i.gtld-servers.net.", "g.gtld-servers.net."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 32768, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av1.nstld.com.", "av2.nstld.com.", "av3.nstld.com.", "av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}, {"answer": [], "flags": 33792, "question": "av4.nstld.com.", "authority": ["av4.nstld.com."]}]